okay - howhow did you have a good
meditation
although didn't forget the Lions dance
earlier they didn't forget the lion
stance okay okay cool okay here's my
plan
[Music]
I'm going to check if you remember what
we did so far the team you have some way
to choose people's names where's Tim
okay I'll just choose and after we
review the sub pictures then I will
teach new things and 10:30 we will
finish our sign book take photo okay and
there will be a line here 10:30 okay so
have your book ready if you don't have
any money to buy a book I will buy okay
all right okay that's all okay let's go
oh I know next Thursday okay good uh did
you do man download this money you
finish okay so let's go you guys ready
Nick first picture okay good
anybody can tell me why this picture is
on the front of your book for 100 baht
$3.00 why is this picture what's the
name of on the front of your book yeah
how to make him mind a beautiful place
okay because we are going to study how
to make your mind more beautiful then I
chose this picture this is your mind
especially the water
and the birds are small thoughts going
to your mind but the mind is very
beautiful okay
that's why we are here that's what we
are doing
okay next picture you guys 100 who could
tell me what's this picture mean you
okay add Edmund
[Applause]
okay very nice you have a good husband
and you have good parents also and the
second meaning is don't spend more than
you make okay you have karma credit card
[Music]
it's okay to have a nice car it's okay
to have a nice house but you must help
other people otherwise you're just using
up your credit card there's a
intelligent way to use your Karma
if you use all of it for yourself
that credit card will go down down down
them if you buy Tesla Model X and you
use it to help Jasmine to bring things
here and there you will make more good
seeds than you use up then Edmond can
also have a Tesla
okay understand it's okay to have nice
things but use them for good purposes
then you won't get karmic seed shortage
in this picture this American lady she
spent more money than she made okay she
bought that Tesla car but she didn't
help and she bought a camera but she
didn't take good pictures and after one
week she has less karma stage than
before one way to make more good sees is
to encourage other people to reinvest
okay so your friends your family you
know when encourage them when you get
some money then it's okay to buy nice
things for your family put your parents
in business class
that's very classy okay that's okay but
same little bit for poor people or to do
some gamma project okay okay then you
don't run out and the best way to make
extra bank account is to encourage other
people to make extra in Muslim they have
very good custom it's called saccade
saccade I think it's one of the five
rules of Muslim and it says every person
income should give like 5 or 10% to
charity it's required every Muslim
person and it's a great custom okay so
we can do the same and if we encourage
our friends to do we make extra good C's
okay today I'm asking you for donation
[Music]
but I'm not you can you can give to my
charity
but even better make your own journey
okay so today I will ask you for getting
Michael's charity but it's more powerful
if you make your own journey okay
each person here you can make your own
change okay it's easy put aside 10% then
you you donate to what you like I like
to tell people put your mother's name on
the charity my mom's nickname her
friends her real name is Elizabeth like
La means Elizabeth I have two big
Elizabeth's in my life but her friends
call her bunky I don't know why bunkie
bunkie so I made a charity it's called a
bunkie charity people ask me what's a
bunkie I say it's my mom
and you can do the same you make your
own charity and you put 10% and then you
you you give to something
earthquake victims in West China
flamenco dancing lessons for poor kids
in Japan okay you decide okay it's more
powerful also give to my tearing okay
next picture this is very deep picture
it has deep meaning
I think it's a hundred dollar picture
two parts here okay two part
I don't know if anyone can guess yeah
some brave brave person two parts
bluffing
[Music]
perfect hundred dollars okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
who's giving the money shopping okay
can you remember it's I have in my bank
okay don't forget okay
I have in my bag but you can do later we
can do minute okay all right
very good answer
camel are Sheila who wrote the famous
explanation of the jinkin gene he said
there are two kinds of people first kind
they are using their car machine okay
they they are burning car machine which
person in the picture on the right side
okay she's burning Herkimer okay she's
drinking some coffee or something
understand she's drinking coffee
the other person is making new scene
okay it's okay to do and then come alive
Sheila says don't be seed either be a
seed producer okay so the person under
layer is producing steam the person on
the right is using thing right no the
person on the right is taking a rest
this is one of the best seeds you can
plan work hard serve other people and
take a rest okay
real Dharma person knows how to relax
very well put on the rock and roll music
have a nice coffee
lay down on the couch eat three pastries
from this restaurant
okay that's what I'm going to do this
afternoon okay so I'm a person it's
important to know how to relax and then
you also make good good seats I'm going
to sit down I'm going to burn some seeds
to have a good coffee and I'm gonna rest
and then when I'm recharge my battery
then I will help a lot of people so
actually I'm just making joke the lady
on the right is probably burning seeds
but it's possible she's like jasmine or
like chin zone she worked very hard to
prepare for this retreat and she's very
intelligent and she knows sometimes she
has to take a rest okay and sometimes
you have to relax and practice rock and
roll with Nick and Aaron okay
and Johnny of4 Clark
okay I understand okay so resting is
also to make good C's okay okay next
picture next picture
I think that the donkey is running the
just kidding in the kids class we had
donkey and tiger okay
all right hundred baht question
okay what's what's this about we covered
it yes go ahead
nice good and nobody nobody pays
attention to her she's not beautiful
maybe she was beautiful now she's not
she's not rich and she's not young and
she cannot do flamenco okay then no one
wants to look at her and this happened
to all people
it means happens to all of us okay there
will come a time we will be all and we
will be alone nobody want to be with us
we are not fun we cannot go play with
other people okay so this is the future
for everybody okay Oh shopping 100
button and they're bad for her
don't forget okay this one's difficult
Mexico people should know like her so
she should know
now he's getting nervous come on we
talked about this in Mexico she has idea
[Music]
perfect answer hey yeah yeah yeah don't
get off too early go to the ninth floor
if you don't reach the teacher in your
meditation you didn't do meditation
show me the first eighth floor she he
got it sugar Ukraine got it she's like
okay just it just warm up okay it's not
the real meditation
okay you don't get olympic medal for
this understand okay
next picture this one's super easy
yeah
good morning Oh previous watch a large
table with broccoli is Kazakhstan okay
cool super perfect
[Applause]
$100 answer okay you get from her okay
after the clip don't forget otherwise
she will keep it I think we should give
Stanley hand for translations
[Applause]
[Music]
okay last one
okay this needs explanation there's a
food in America it's a vegetable called
eggplant eggplant you have in China okay
geshe michael hate this verse okay super
him okay I really don't like this then I
went to pass recently with my partner
and we asked our friend Ben what's a
good restaurant and he told us to look a
pool like a pool right and a stage his
sister also sent me to a good restaurant
she lives in Paris so my partner say I'm
order for you I said what am I having
they brought this thing I said Western
Oh oppa gene aubergine Z this is
aubergine I said this is not OB g this
is eggplant
don't give a good name don't put
different-looking don't think I don't
understand eggplant okay I don't want to
be easy okay same crap different package
okay same crap different package
okay so Xiao ping give getting micro
hundred dollar
now we're gonna do
okay and we'll we'll go for about an
hour okay okay here we go we have to do
more
I'm a drunk Chuck you guys are a and
Jeep space CAG Nick I'm a drunk Chuck
our ang space CAG run Chucky katakana
m'dear
Korean dinner they were in sunbaenim
camp so we think I understand this is
sansara I understand I understand I'm in
the wheel of rebirth
I understand but gasner not everything
is suffer you know sometimes the hotel
will make a nice coffee
[Music]
it tastes good to me okay and I enjoy so
we are in some service but some things
are nice something's feel good then he
said then the Daniel contraction shot on
that coffee also suffering it's the
llama Center okay Tanya Union Barnum
contended in your connection thing then
gas law
some things are just neutral there is a
grass outside then I don't care much
about it you know Jasmine never let me
to go outside
so I mean it doesn't really matter to me
and that's not suffering okay then the
llama here said no it's also suffering
things which seem like happiness are
suffering even the things which seem
like neutral they are also suffering
[Music]
mandates our dinner silver topper neck
up they were torn on toboni then if you
burn your hand while you are cooking and
blister will come it has a water inside
[Music]
then it feels bad it feels hot and if
you put it under the cold water it it
feels okay but that's illusion actually
you have a bad
blister
so for a few minutes it feels okay
but that's illusion then the nature is
suffering okay Tama in the corner on its
own they were there they mean I'm cheap
Anna young dunya keeping on when you
stop putting the cold water it will
start to hurt again okay so you get a
coffee for a few minutes but if you stop
it then the natural natural nature will
come back such suffering okay and this
coffee is the second kind of suffering
what's that suffering I'm change why did
things change seed finish okay seed made
this coffee maybe you know I used to
make a lot of tea for my la Mer many
years I made tea for him so result
that's it open I see coffee on the table
someone brought gas in our coffee
okay it come from my seeds okay but
every time okay what count 104 seconds
of coffee
250 seeds use up use up okay like 250
cup of tea from my teacher like that
okay it's a difficult business coffee
karma business okay and the seed will
finish then maybe I don't have coffee
maybe I don't have a mouth to drink the
coffee because that seed also finish
okay when when you use things you're
using seeds patients are check if they
were time jaded on same thing is semsem
to in Tom Jaudon kana meaning he will
use such in an idiot you know and every
experience we have we are listening to
music we are spending time with our
children we are using our seeds okay all
the time and it will change
children will get all the music you know
will go mile did so what number cubed
some not so we don't know so make them
sorry wrong shin do young man
so our body is like a blister the nature
is painful sometimes you get a coffee or
someone give you massage you feel better
for 10 minutes 15 minutes during the
massage time your body getting older
if the massage start at 9 o'clock and
the massage finish at 10 o'clock you
feel better right yeah you feel good you
got one hour massage but in the
background your body is one hour older
you are one hour closer to the thing
that will kill you
so is the massage suffering or not
suffering your one hour closer to cancer
you are one hour closer to your heart
okay so it it it looks like pleasure
okay so I'm gonna take a break today I'm
gonna go get a massage but during the
massage you are walking closer to your
death okay all right
when Candela chile's up at Salonga defy
God my tip in their capital benissa
check it so at Oneonta Terrance in the
distance and to you than ship and I'm
counting in nimesh I want to go change
denied on your mama team and I'm Kelly
sobbing Jethro I think under joining
England and Jesse over now cabbage
ad-dunya okay
it means now important idea is coming we
had in Sheng Jian Chen Wang
what's the sense goodnight for $10 $20
$30 $40 cancel it did he say anything
but it para tanto para Tantra okay you
have to talk fast with me okay someone
means you don't have power it's like you
are working in a company for a very mean
boss maybe you experienced this special
stuffing of mean boss not Jesse okay
your boss is very sweet okay so ya mean
boss okay mean boss come to you at 15
minutes before 5 o'clock you know in
Price Waterhouse
Oh Edmond you did a great job you've
been working hard on being it's almost
five o'clock time to go home and see
your wife and child then he say but when
the Bostick done sure there's a problem
but we have a special project it's very
unusual right very rare special project
my boss he's very smart okay if he say
you have to stay after five o'clock then
at that time I was doing my gosh I study
then I I made a deal with him I will
take half salary but I must go home at
five o'clock because my teacher teaches
at seven o'clock and it's a two-hour so
this is our agreement sometimes people
try to threaten me you know he would say
at 4:45 right we have special projects
you have to stay after fun you have to
stay until 7:00 o'clock then I'm like
that's not our agreement then he look at
me like this you know so you don't like
working here no I like working here
yeah but it's okay to get fired right
he's threatening me you know then I'm
like okay fire me I will clean out my
desk no he's like okay go you know in
English we play play chicken we call
play chicken
he will go like this I will fire you
then I I'm like check he's serious or
not okay fire me okay go home like that
later he learned very smart maybe your
boss does 4:45 call you to the office
Mike you know in this company you are
the big bodies of
without you we we are lost we don't know
what to do
only you can do the special party you
are special person if you go home all of
us will cry then I'm like okay I was
dead then he's like okay go stay here's
a job he tricked me
okay so anyway why am I talking about
them
oh yeah it means that we don't have
power the boss has power okay we have to
do it the boss says okay if you work for
other person they have the power you
don't have the power why are we talking
about that now
[Music]
this book is going to go a special way
to explain power who has the power
okay who's the boss of your life okay
who's the boss of you and I and there's
two famous bosses okay there are two
famous bosses of your life well there's
three right first one is your wife okay
second one is karma third one is your
negative emotion
and now the book is going to explain
long explanations all the kinds of
negative emotions okay anger jealousy
desire pride okay misunderstanding okay
all those the garbage in the money okay
if we can clean them we will have a
beautiful mind
okay right now the mind is not beautiful
okay damn lot of garbage makes it dirty
okay so he's gonna explain it
he's going to spend a lot of time about
it and we're gonna go there
[Music]
yeah so I'm gonna go to he have a little
bit more to say about suffering Nick I'm
at parody PE RNA dpe RNA okay fair
enough
okay been a thunder long right did man
did talk we feel we go outside to enjoy
that I saw this morning people enjoy the
ocean so we asked our friend let's go
outside let's go and join the ocean then
you go out to the beach you know and for
like 15 minutes it's very pleasant then
start to get sunburned you know then you
then you change your mind I think I'd
like to go inside you know so you go to
your room and it's nice no heart no stun
everything's nice after 2 hours you feel
bored I like to go get some fresh air
then you go outside to the Sun oh it's
so nice you know I'm so happy we're in
Thailand you know then after two hours
Sun is too hard
I would like to go inside like that this
is story of our life when did the pain
start outside when did it start
when did the uncomfortable start outside
when you step aside no geshe-la the
first two hours was a pleasure
no the suffering was getting bigger okay
the suffering was going but you didn't
notice okay there's a very famous story
in American English the guy walked down
the road then he saw a man the man is
hitting his head on the wall
like that you know stop that don't do
that well why are you doing that it
feels so good when I stop understand you
go out in the Sun suffering starts but
you don't know this okay then it gets
bigger and bigger finally say I want to
go inside okay so our whole life is just
suffering are bigger suffering are
smaller suffering a bigger it's nothing
got smart this is our noise
you won't be happy anywhere you don't
have capacity to be happy because you
have bad since you are under the power
of a bad to bad bosses your old karma
and your all negative emotions okay and
they are connected I had a when I was 26
I was in the month day for about five
six years and I'm like the only man who
knows how to drive a car then very high
Lama Kim then they they said can you
drive the car
I said yeah I won't try you know then
they said when he gets in the car don't
talk to him I'm like why he's a real
Yamantaka okay killer of death one who
kills death you know
thirteen eyes four heads big you know
don't don't don't talk to him okay I'm
like okay you know then come time to
drive it's about a three hour drive then
three big Lamas got in the car you know
then he sit in the front then the llama
behind this very high lama he's still
alive he's 95 he told the other high
number
Oh Mike is learning very good
he learned abhidhamma which 10 is
teaching today then the big romantic
anonymous couple non-date Angela
magician and you know longer than he
ever did and it wasn't me then I was
lucky because I studied it yesterday I
said oh that's the second chapter such
as original number of additional such a
closet that is a nakida give again I'm
at the Village Inn and such an conceited
and a son I'm gonna give a year now got
Daniel Cobain wasn't me but I'm like I
don't know he's like you know dinner we
are dry he said how old are you then I'm
supposed to stay in West China language
I'm supposed to say 26 I'm so scared I
said 62
[Laughter]
lilies like hahaha no no 26 2000 good
luck good luck you're gonna live long
line then okay dry enjoy then we are
driving you know and I'm trying not to
tire then in in the back the two big
llama fall asleep like I'm doing you
know
then this your month ago hey you what
when we drive to America I never came to
America you tell me what what are these
things we we came to graveyard
you know Christian people like to bury
under the ground then he's like what's
that graveyard
what's that when people die did they dig
under the ground put the bunny ha ha ha
what a waste of space
[Laughter]
good I'm driving you know this thing the
cars too hard turn down the air
conditioning okay turn on the engine see
in five minutes the cars too cold
turn out the anything too hot too cold
come on - go ahead you think I'm crazy
no no no now please
yeah okay then we talked for two hours
we had a really fun time I won't I will
never forget that joy but after that
many days I thought why he'd do this
thing with the air conditioning
he's not crazy but look crazy then it's
always the big llama
try to teach you something
you know and after once he tried to
teach me you know with the air
conditioner then when I reach this
teaching in the lamrim then I realize oh
he was teaching me this so you have to
watch those romantic they will they will
give you teaching in the car okay my
teacher when we drive he will say turn
left then then I I know it's the wrong
way
tell my mom I said turn left
maybe there's a big car accident on the
right maybe I will die if I turn right
okay turn left okay understand okay
pendant Danielle data they did attempt
at some container GPL tuition the new
months um they can meet them I'm a
potato coupon day that I'm in too much
I'm saying it in your day so he's
talking about the air conditioner same
thing when you sit too long in the
lamrim class you know I hope yes I will
take a break we are sitting for a long
time then your friend said let's go for
a walk on the beach you know my body is
sore we sit too long in alarm in class
then you walk then your feet get sore
then you're like I think I like to sit
down then you sit down then after I
don't know half-hour your body's sore
again then it's a body problem body is
the problem you cannot make it happy
impossible okay you always want
something else
the attending a patient in
so the problem he says even and oh by
the way somebody asked me a question
yesterday in that DCI gala you always
say we should be superhero we should be
like Iron Man or spider-man yesterday in
the class you said the superheroes bad
they are suffering they are burning up
good karma so which one is correct this
is two different superheroes okay I'm
sorry if I confuse you okay
I'm using movie superhero just as an
example for those powerful guys who
don't understand the pen okay like rich
people in this world who don't
understand the pen okay I'm just using
for example okay so this week when I
said superhero
I mean rich people powerful people but
they don't understand the pen so there
are burning seeds but they're not making
new ones okay
in the DCI we teach how to use it to
make money how do you see to have a
happy marriage how do you see to be
healthy how do you seem to make a
peaceful mind but if you just make
yourself rich and you have nice marriage
and your body is strong but everybody
else doesn't know how to do it then it's
not fun to be healthy you feel bad you
are make easy money and your friends
don't have money it's like you go to the
restaurant you have money you buy
expensive Japanese meal you know we had
in Shenzhen and then nobody else can
afford
so imagine everybody else is looking in
the window and they are hungry and you
are yourself you are eating alone many
poor people looking at you
is it fun to eat like that it feels
uncomfortable you know poor people
looking and you are eating dessert then
to eat to have success for yourself
it feels lonely
so we want to share with other people
how to share with other people there's
two methods okay one method is to teach
them take them to Thailand
talk talk talk talk talk talk talk
okay this is one method to teach people
okay success
the second method just be successful
okay
make a lot of money have beautiful
partner do ballet when you are 65 have
peaceful mind okay
human advertisement okay
then people will come to you Stanley
how do you make so much money where you
get such a beautiful partner
are you also pretty healthy what's your
secret
okay understand that's a living example
devoid premier parlors kita living
example how do you say in in espanol
exam you'll be gente yeah something like
that yeah okay so why I'm talking about
that why we like those superhero movies
why we like them so much
Iron Man save whole world that stupid
kid what's his name transformer in a
transformer movie number one he's a real
stupid kid he's a messenger in the
company then he got the three principal
paths he got the son bow he got the
blonde girlfriend he got the fast car
and he saved the whole world okay the
most important one first the
girlfriend's second most important he
got the car and third he stayed the
whole world understand how many times
transformer one transformer transformer
three okay why they keep making those
movies as people like them why do people
like them they want to be the boy who
saved the world and they want the
girlfriend in the car okay then why they
enjoy the movie they want to be
Supergirl so all of us in our life when
we are I don't know 10 12 years old we
ask ourself questions why why I came
here why I came to this world you know
why was I born where I was born what am
I supposed to do and we feel hungry you
know there are three great hungers
inside of people number one food we like
food all human like food number two sex
we are like thanks three-and-a-half
billion women looking for three and a
half billion men three and a half
billion men looking for three and a half
billion women
[Music]
this is the world is that in that gene
abhidhamma these are the two great
desires of a person but there's a third
one I want to state the world I want to
help every person it's stronger than a
food desire it's stronger than sex
difference okay and everybody has it we
all have it okay if you learn the pen if
you use it to become successful you can
be spider-man better than spider-man
okay better than ant-man
you will be a transformer and number
four will be you understand so that's
the second meaning of superhero okay
understand first meaning that's those
guys who don't know the pen which rich
rich rich rich guys but they don't know
the pimp then they will just get old
they will die they will lose the money
okay second superhero is pens superhero
okay and they are successful and they're
happy they know how to reinvest this
scene and they know how to help other
people
okay that's what I mean when I say pens
will be here you should be the pencil
before you shouldn't be the other
superhero who very powerful didn't die
okay okay so two separate superiors okay
stay with me okay we need to do more
twenty more minutes okay I know you're
tired okay I know your body's tired my
teacher say I know he talked like this
right he had a car accident
he talks just like Star Wars I know you
are tired he was sitting a long time the
room is too cold
sometimes room is too hard
you have to pee-pee right now I
understand then he goes like this
but I don't care we have 20 more minutes
he's like that that's my my teachers
stuff okay so he said the problem is the
body and the mind when we were born we
took a body and in mind it's like when
you are born you land in the airport and
you go and you rent a car they will give
you a car this one okay and this one and
when you are born they will give you a
body and they will give you a mind then
that body has a problem it you cannot
make it happy it will turn on the
air-conditioner will turn off the air
conditioner it will go out to the beach
it will come away from the beach it will
go to Thailand for vacation it will come
home because I love home you know it
will drive you to move move move okay
you cannot make her happy and the mind
also Oh Stanley I apply for a job
and really great company you know number
one accounting company I hope I get the
job yeah then you get the job I got the
time okay let's go to dinner
let's go celebrate six weeks later Danny
I hate this job
you know I have to work so hard
boss never happy okay it's an ATAR I met
a new boy yeah he's so cute he likes me
lucky six weeks later I hate him more
than any other person in the world
ex-wife ex-husband Hey
okay it's it's not the person it's not
the job it's our own mind it's defective
when they gave you the rental car they
gave you defective car okay
this part and this body okay and you
cannot be happy in this body in this
money it's not possible you will always
want to go understand and you always
want to come back in it son
you will always want the boy and then
you will always be tired of the brain
it's not the boy I'll tell you
interesting experiment you can try you
can try it okay
go into a room with ten people okay go
into a room with ten other people after
one hour three of them you will like
them three of them you will not like
four of them you don't care
okay three three and four now take the
three that you like and take seven more
that you like put them in a second room
and spend an hour with them after an
hour you will like three of them you
will not like three of them and for them
you will not care about them it's okay
your mind is thirty thirty forty mine
from the factory okay it's broken from
the factory tender Bumbo Tiberium from
Balu Dubnyk jung yonghwa dumped on you
step a socket Daniel no another dog
sugar tubes simple day even a donkey has
taken a party and people will put things
on it and people will hit it and this is
the nature of their body darkness mi
cheese soup an army sleeping outside -
not soon shaken their link you fumbled
in Long Bay chew onion once you have a
body something will happen to it okay
even just a thorn on a rose small pink
whole day will come it's not the world
problem it's a body problem okay you
have wrong kind of body you can you
cannot make this bunny happy you cannot
make this mind happy it's defective
okay it's the wrong body we got in the
wrong body
difficult to get out okay then i'm each
ever got to say my Corsica Romana they
call poke mass em but they sitting under
my tuition so if you take a big bunch of
nails put them in a bag put them on
Stanley's back it will hurt some of some
of them were hurt and until he takes the
bag off it will hurt if you are born in
this body it will hurt things will hurt
okay until the day you die
okay we must change the body okay like
take off shirt okay we have to take off
this body and you can do it okay it's
possible you can get a new model okay a
good one okay all right Buddha buddy
what's Buddha body look like my
Christian friends he came to visit me in
the monastery I took him to see the
temple because it's so beautiful then he
he'd look at everything you know then
when we left a temper
he said guess I I don't know why your
Buddhist you know I said what's wrong he
said those Buddhist you know who wants
to be like that I said what's wrong with
the Buddha this big bump on his head
long ear you know doesn't look very nice
I don't know why you Buddhists you have
to understand sometimes I tell my
students go by if it's a girl I say go
by Vogue magazine pick the most
beautiful woman that's you when you
become Buddha the guys have to buy GQ
magazine the handsome guy you know and
you can choose ok it means when you
become Buddha you are the most beautiful
body you can imagine super beautiful
okay and cannot die and never pain okay
never peepee poo-poo okay save a lot of
time okay boys don't have to shave all
the time okay beautiful body okay so
don't think oh I don't want the bump
I don't want fat belly like this Buddha
you know okay
not like that you will be the most
elegant and exquisite thing you can
imagine
and no pain I cannot have pain we have
to change the body this one is even if
you do yoga even if you eat still it's a
problem still it will get on still it
will get cancer okay so we want to
change it okay
some people say poor poor you get that
don't worry you can do poor when you die
you do special prayer at that time you
will go to Buddha body it's impossible
for one person out of a billion okay to
do poor it's possible okay one person
out of a billion can can do can do poor
okay you can wait until the last minute
and then get your Buddha body but it's
dangerous okay
ninety-nine percent fail okay so take
care of it now you have to go home from
Thailand in two days three days so pack
your suitcase today then enjoy for two
days you don't have to think about it
okay get the Buddha body now don't wait
for last day of your life
okay maybe you will probably you will
fail okay so change the body now learn
how to change the body now we call
living diamond okay the body is the
living dumber how to how to get that
body there's a special scene what's the
scene see honking directly okay see
function directly okay in that moment so
when you get cancer
my friend has cancer and it's very sad
she's a beautiful person and she got
breast pant cancer then it start to grow
and small one cell breaks okay and then
it starts to break uncontrollable and
actually the body is rotting from the
inside okay like old banana or something
you know you open in this morning I had
a banana like that outside looks good
then the Sun wasn't up yet you know and
I opened the banana it outside looked
fine inside got a rotten so this is what
cancer
skin is still here but inside this
erotic you know and it's it's very sad
usually you cannot stop it okay if it
start you can slow it down but you can't
stop it okay then if you see coaching
it's the opposite then one shall become
living time then to sell become living
diamond then three star become the link
inside so at that moment when you see
coaching directly the body start like
Buddha cancer start from the inside and
then your body start to change and then
nothing can stop it there's no cure for
Buddha body okay if you start the first
self it will spend and your body become
deathless and very beautiful and no pain
and your relatives can learn also okay
so if you see coating directly it it it
it starts the process
and you cannot stop it even if you
understand caution it makes a change
inside and you cannot go to the health
okay you cannot go to element okay
something changed inside okay so that's
why we teach the pan over and over we
had a kid class then we asked each kid
what's the nicest thing your mom did for
you and they all said different things
then we said okay what's the nicest
thing you ever did for your mom I think
it was at that time one kid said I
taught my mom the parenting minute
that's a real cool okay very cool by the
way those kids also know the four steps
very well so I think your parents are
doing a good job
[Applause]
I taught a kid's class for 15 years in
New York I did it confession it was a
confession I had an abortion when I was
in college and I didn't I wasn't
Buddhist so I didn't understand then I
told my teacher when I was younger I had
abortion then he said he said you have
to clean this scene then I said how to
clean the scene he said I think you you
destroyed a child so you should teach
children and then I said how long is
then until the city's finished then like
how long is that
he said you you want you will know your
heart will feel happy when that seat is
finished your heart will feel much
different until that time your heart
will feel heavy then I didn't realize it
but I checked my heart and I realized
he's correct I feel some thing Stan
so I said what should I do
he said maybe a teacher children's class
so I started children's class with the
children's parents and with the parents
of the children with their permission
and they come to the class then I taught
them the pan I taught them the fourth
dance then I there's a beautiful story
one day in New York is very hot in the
summer
it's Beijing I don't know in the summer
so usually in New York is pretty nice
because it's on the ocean but in the
summer it's very unpleasant and it's
very hot very wet and we used air
conditioning then I'm teaching the kids
class I taught for fifteen years before
I feel change in my heart so one day air
conditioner broke
and I have to climb up a ladder and I'm
trying to fix their air conditioner you
know then one of the kids is pulling on
my pant leg I like later later
stop I'm fixing the air conditioner then
he keeps pulling on my pants like stop
stop I have to face it
they said teacher I saw one so what are
you doing I'm fixing the air
conditioning what it's hard to air
conditioner that's not the way to fix
the air conditioner what's the way to
fix the air conditioner you go outside
you find other person there air
conditioner broke you fix their air
conditioners
[Applause]
if you did that yesterday I recognition
won't break today okay so kids learn
better than adults okay yeah okay
mandala offering
by Christie from Kanto
[Applause]
she became she marathon timer vc and egg
and paddy sang guarantor maintain
[Music]
ye drunkard and she lies hip
so good
yeah
[Music]
the Kellogg son Amish a tautology
surname from way
[Music]